<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gérard Paligot</title><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/</link><description>Recent content on Gérard Paligot</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 14:44:08 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gerard.paligot.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/blog/</guid><description>Blog 2022 SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer 2021 Jetpack Compose: How to play with Canvas? Sharing Compose components between Android and Desktop 2020 Jetpack Compose: How to make a scrollable list? Jetpack Compose: How to handle states inside a Composable? Jetpack Compose: How to write conditional Composable?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/speaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/speaking/</guid><description>Speaking 2023 Sunny Tech - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page, slides, Openfeedback) Mobilis In Mobile 2023 - Take your shot of Vitamin! (event page, slides, OpenFeedback) Android Makers by droidcon - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page, slides, Openfeedback) DevDay - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page, slides, Openfeedback) FOSDEM'23 - Take your shot of Vitamin! (event page, video, slides) FRAUG - App-Clinic #3 (event page, video) 2022 FRAUG - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page, slides, video, Openfeedback) Devfest Strasbourg - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page) Devfest Nantes - L&amp;rsquo;accessibilité, c&amp;rsquo;est pas sorcier (event page, video, slides, Openfeedback) VolcampIO - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page, Openfeedback) Meetup LAUG - SwiftUI vs Jetpack Compose by an Android Engineer (event page, video, Openfeedback) Droidcon Italy - Accessibility with Compose: Experimentation &amp;amp; Live coding (event page, Openfeedback) Meetup GDG Nantes Android - From Jetpack Compose to Compose Multiplatform (event page, Openfeedback) Meetup PAUG - Highlight Android from Google IO 2022 (event page, video, slides) Adeo Dev Summit - L&amp;rsquo;accessibilité, c&amp;rsquo;est pas sorcier (event page, slides) Android Makers - L&amp;rsquo;accessibilité, c&amp;rsquo;est pas sorcier (event page, video, slides, Openfeedback) BBL Decathlon - L&amp;rsquo;accessibilité, c&amp;rsquo;est pas sorcier (slides, Openfeedback) Touraine Tech - Discovering Jetpack Compose (event page, slides) 2021 Devfest Strasbourg - Discovering Jetpack Compose (event page, video, slides) Adeo Dev Summit - Mobile Platform Engineering, how to standardize mobile practice in your company?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round1/compose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round1/compose/</guid><description>Round 1</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round1/swiftui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round1/swiftui/</guid><description>Round 1 Wait, really?! Why are you at Android Makers?! 😱</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round2/compose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round2/compose/</guid><description>Round 2</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round2/swiftui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round2/swiftui/</guid><description>Round 2 Did you really listen to me?!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round3/compose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round3/compose/</guid><description>Round 3</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round3/swiftui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round3/swiftui/</guid><description>Round 3 Meh?! Xcode previews are cool but not better than Android Studio ones!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round4/compose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round4/compose/</guid><description>Round 4</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round4/swiftui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gerard.paligot.com/swiftui-vs-compose/round4/swiftui/</guid><description>Round 4 Ok SwiftUI appears that this technology have some good design decisions but wait for the end! 😈</description></item></channel></rss>